Guide to the Stanford Cohort Study Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford cohort study records
undated
SC0599
Stanford cohort study.
26 linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-2000-184
  - Cohort follow-up typology (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cream of the crop-permissions (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cohort study follow-up sample (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cohort study follow-up other interviewers (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cohort follow-up memos to interview team (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Cohort follow-up interviewers and interviewees (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Corp. Award (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Cohort follow-up administration (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Cohort study follow-up coding instructions (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Cohort follow-up correspondence to interviewees (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cohort follow-up address list and telephone numbers (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cohort follow-up interview guide (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cohort follow-up data files on rate (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Ideas for follow-up (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cohort follow-up study misc. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cohort Follow-up study plans (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Coding Tables (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Misc. Figures (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Undergraduate Learning at the University of Virginia (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Cohort follow-up study strober account (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Coming of Age Table of Contents (draft) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 4-year comparison questionnaire (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Jossey Bass Publishers, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Careerism…Student Responses (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - School of Education--Ray Bacchetti (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Freshman Questionnaires (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Freshman Questionnaire (1978): Variable Dictionary (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Freshman Questionnaire--Drafts of Coding Tables--Open-ended Questions (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Freshman Questionnaire (1978): Coding Instructions (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Sophomore Questionnaires and Interview Outlines (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Sophomore Questionnaire (1979): Coding Instructions (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Addendum to Sophomore Questionnaire (1979): Coding Instructions (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Junior Questionnaires (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Coding Instructions: Junior Questionnaire. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Addendum to Junior Questionnaire (1980): Coding Instructions (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Junior Questionnaire: Coding Instructions 1979-80 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Tables of Transfer Responses to Junior Questionnaire (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Appendix to Cohort Book (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Senior Questionnaire Original (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Senior Coding Instructions, Including Tables (all 60 of them) Hollingshead (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Senior Questionnaire (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Standardized Cohort Files and Archive Files (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Senior Questionnaire Tables 9/82 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - 1981 Senior Cohort Mailing (what was mailed to students) (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 1980-1, Senior Survey Reports (Cohorts Only) (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Senior Questionnaire Results (modified form) (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Cohort Luncheon Invitation (senior year) (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - File 8 Coding Instructions (admissions information) (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Senior Interview Guidelines (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Curric. Study Article (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Katchadourian/Boli figures (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Retreat 1980 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Retreat 1979 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Spencer Foundation Proposal 7/10/80 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - SUES--Humanities Team Mahoney (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - SUES—Engineering Team Adams (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - SUES—Natural Science Team Bacchetti (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - SUES—Social Science Team Hargadon (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - SUES—Pre-Medicine Team Katchadourian (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Responses to initial letter thoughts on freshman experience (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Intuitive Ratings of Students (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Approval of Panel on Human Subjects (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Photos from Cohort Picnic (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Interviewing Team (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Sampling Ratios for Transfer Students Data Files (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cohort Participation Information (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Cohort Flag in SMAC files of Oasis, Registrar's Files (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Student Residence (Escondido) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Participants' Permanent Addresses (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Master List Participants (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Transfer Students (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Junior Transfer Sample (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Abrahamson, Murray Alan (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Adicoff, Samuel David (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Agnew, Karen Beryl (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Agnew, Mark William (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Aguilar, Elizabeth L. C. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Agustinez, Anecita S. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Allen, Hugh Willison (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Allen, Richard Jeffery (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Allio, Michael Gregory (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Anaradian, Leon (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Anderson, Christina R. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Anderson, Judy Gale (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Anderson, William D. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Andrews, Linda Kay (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Angelchik, Paul David (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Acher, Shirley J. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Barnett, Laurey Jean (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Begley, Diana Lynn (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Bellavia, Thomas C. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Bernstein, Barbara (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Bickford, Martha Elise (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Biggar, Michael John (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Bjornson, Dana Lloyd (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Blackstock, Robert K. B. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Bloom, Keith David (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Blumberg, Alan Mark (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Boly, Richard (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Bonini, Julie Mary (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Boonyakurkul, Pakorn (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bottorff, Charles M., Jr. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bowden, Anne Maureen (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bowman, Timothy Lee (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bradford, Ethan Robert (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bradley, Steven Adam (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bralove, Drue Allison (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Brase, David Edward (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Braun, Evan (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Brentari, Ruth Michelle (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Eichhoff, Kim Marie (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Eimon, Ted Arthur (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Eldredge, Susan Allen (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Ellis, William John (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Des George, Rose P (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Doi, Kathryn Ellen (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Dolan, Colleen J. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Dupree, Michael Joseph (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Durfee, Molly Rose (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Costello, Peter Wood (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Crane, Eloise Porter (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Curotto, Dina Lynn (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Daley, Dawn Gabriele (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Daniels, Andrew M. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - David, Richard Daniel (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Davidson, Peter Warner (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Davis, Cheryl Ann (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Dearmond, Laura (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Cassell, Paul George (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Childs, Dennis Lee (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Chun, Paul K. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Coleman, Ina Wyn (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Corbett, Jason Daniel (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bridges, Rebecca Ruth (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Brock, Joel Donald (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Brolley, Wolfgang Edward (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brown, Charles Clendon (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Monte Dean (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bunting, William B. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Burns, Charles Rowe (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Canizales, Albert James (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Carrillo, Juanita Jo (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - William Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Jaime Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Roy Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Ronald Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Mark Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Jeanne Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Dan Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Rebecca Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Albert Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - David Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Eric Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Vanessa Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Heidi Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Jeff Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Scott Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Marie Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Tom Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Paul Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Steve Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Patti Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Patricia Titus Senior Survey (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Mark Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Martin Fuentes Senior Survey (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Juanita Cohort Interview (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Jo Interview Report (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Ernst, Ruth Marie (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Eschelman, Lori Rae (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Etchemendy, Jeanne M. (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Euwer, Jennifer Anne (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Ewing, Kevin Douglas (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Fam, Samia Azer (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Farrington, Deborah Ann (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Fay, Todor Christopher (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Fearon, Robert Scott (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Felder, Lawrence James (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Fields, Barbara Irene (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Fitzgerald, John Thomas (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Fradkin, Steven Russell (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Freeman, Victoria Lynn (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Friedberg, Thomas W. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Frieman, Joshua Adam (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fuentes, Martin Keith (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Fulmer, Alma Leigh (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Gallagher, Theresa C. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Gardner, Douglas Adam (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Gardner, James Conrad (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Girvin, Sally Ruth (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Goldfarb, Susan V. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Gomez, Isidro Joseph (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Grasmeder, Henry M. III (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Greene, George Marlin (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Gresser, Lawrence T. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Grown, Tracey Lynn (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Gueble, Jeffrey Raymond (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Guerrero, David (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Guttman, Monika Adele (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Haldeman, Ann Kurtz (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Hale, David Lee (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Halper, James David (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Hampton, Jaime Jennifer (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Hanson, Gary Robert (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Harrington, Kristen (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Lori Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Glenn Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Robert Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Randy Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - David Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Kevin Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Bill Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Bob Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - David Hale Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Colleen Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Paul Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Family Background (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Sandra Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Teresa Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - John Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Lawrence Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Christina Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Murray Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Valencia Cohort Interview (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Harris, Kathleen Ann (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Harvey, Alan Wayne (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Hatcher, Sylvia Valene (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Hawkins, John William (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Hawkins, Penelope Joyce (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Haxton, Marie Louise (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Hecksher, Madeline E. (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Hedlund, Heidi Lynne (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Heinz, Bradley Donald (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Hernandez, Nora Jean (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Heyman, Jeffrey Dorn (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Hill, Alec Michael (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Hillberg, Ann Marie (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Hilliard, Margaret V. P. (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Hirsch, Jennifer (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Hoch, Andrea Lynn (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Hodge, Elizabeth T. (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Hoffman, Paul Robert (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Hough, Janice Ellen (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Howley, William Edward (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Hsia, Robert (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Hsu, Rita J. (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Hughes, Ralph Gregory (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Huginnie, Jene Denise (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Jackson, Joseph H. III (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Jacobson, Eric Dudley (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Jamison, Susan Kimberley (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Janssen, James Robert (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Sheila Maria (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Jordan, Kathryn (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Joyce, Jean Marie (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Jue, Bill Marshall (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Kakiuchi, Mariko K. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Kammerer, Patricia Lyn (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Assessment Class of 1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Kathleen Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mimi Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Jody Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Jennifer Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Jene Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Jaclyn Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Ken Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Barbara Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Eileen Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Ann Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Kevin Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Gayle Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Carol Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Kenneth Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Ethan Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Ted Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Kathryn Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Paul Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Jaclyn Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Lois Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Leslie Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Leslie Moulton Sr. Survey (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Anne Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Judy Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Hyla Cohort Interview (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Kanner, Jaclyn Andrea (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Karlin, Anna Rochelle (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Keller, William Downs (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Kelly, Kerry Ann (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Kelsall, Brian Lee (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Kemby, Katherine Helen (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Kerber, Mark Alan (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Kern, Kathryn Johnson (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Kesslin, Kenneth Lee (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Kilday, Raymond Joseph (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Kindall, Gregory Lavon (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Kirkpatrick, Jeffrey D. (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Knight, John Knox (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Kurfirst, Leonard S. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - La Brie, Judith Loyola (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Lakhani, Amin Mohammed (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Landis, John Bartle (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Langlotz, Curtis P. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Launer, Alan Eugene (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Le, An-My Thi (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Leavitt, Russell Wayne (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Lee, Steven Robert (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Leland, John Davis (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Lemieux, Ronald Scott (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Leonard, Christopher (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Leonard, Danton (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Lepape, Jeanne Carolyn (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Lerdal, Mark David (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Lesjack, Catherine Anne (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Lewis, Kristin Beth (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Liu, Diane (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Lobsinger, Thomas (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Lockard, William Brodie (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Loer, Curtis Mitchell (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Logan, Patrick Thomas (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Lopatin, Gerald Glen (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Juanita Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Kathleen Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Ina Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Susan Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Ericka Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Jill Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Steve Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Susan Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Jean Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - David Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Lisa Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Linda Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Peter Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Richard Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Richard Sr. Survey (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Joel Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Joel Sr. Survey (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Nora Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Greg Cohort Interview (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Lowry, Stephanie Louise (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Luetkehans, Kirk Joseph (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Lundblad, James Robert (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Mack, Valencia Gaye (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Markel, Barbara Anne (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Martinez, Raoul Patrick (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Maxwell, Deborah Lynn (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Maxwell, Stephan Trevor (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Mayes, Eileen Margaret (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - McCormack, Anne Louise (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - McCracken, Kevin Dunne (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - McGinnis, Gayle Rita (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - McKitterick, Gary S. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - McLaughlin, Michael S. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - McNamara, Pauline Marie (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - McCallion, Heather Lynn (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - McNevin, Daniel Emmett (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Meal, Margaret Allison (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Meland, Donald Albert (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Menon, Victor Paul (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Meyer, Reula Anna (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Milan, John Edward (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Militello, Michael Mark (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Miller, Shari Kay (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Mita, Roy Takashi (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Mitchell, Steven Corson (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Miyake, Tetsuo Ted (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Morales, Gilbert John (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Moulton, Leslie (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Moulton, Peter Humphrey (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Moy, Elizabeth Gabriel (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Nascimento, Antoinette (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Neisser, Sandra Jean (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Nelson, Barbara Jean (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Chuck Cohort Interview (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Jaime Cohort Interview (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Alexander Cohort Interview (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Alexander Sr. Survey (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Darrin Cohort Interview (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Susan Cohort Interview (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Chris Cohort Interview (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Lyle Cohort Interview (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Lyle Sr. Survey (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Jeffrey Cohort Interview (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Ted Cohort Interview (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Joe Cohort Interview (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Tyrone Cohort Interview (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Tyrone Sr. Survey (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Victor Cohort Interview (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Nelson, Darrin M. (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Nesbitt, Lois Ellen (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Nevin, Shirin June (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Northfield, Karin Marie (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - O'Reilly, Michael T. (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Ogden, Lori Jean (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Olivas, Daniel Anthony (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Olmsted, Scott Alan (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Olson, Bradley Charles (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Pappas, Stephen Robert (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Park, Eun Grace (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Park, Linda Sue (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Parker, Diane Elizabeth (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Paul, Mimi (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Pearlman, David Ari (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Penny, Selwyn Andre (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Peter, Kenneth Brian (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Petitt, Matthew Gordon (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Pichon, Patricia Irene (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Piotti, Scott Edward (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Plummer, Cheri Ann (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Pollak, Jody Michael (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Porter, John Elliott (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Pottharst, Hyla Marian (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Powell, Tyrone Anthony (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Radin, Peter M., Jr. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Ramos, Penelope (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Range, Gregory Paul (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Refkin, Randy Scott (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Rianhard, Carl Jory (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Rice, Nancy Katulani (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Rice, Patrick Douglas (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Richards, Renee Anne (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Richards, Ted Eugene (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Ring, William Lee (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Robledo, Basil (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Brad Cohort Interview (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Penelope Hawkins Cohort Interview (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Drue Cohort Interview (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Emily Cohort Interview (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Scott Cohort Interview (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Shari Cohort Interview (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Shari Sr. Survey (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Eloise Cohort Interview (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Teresa Cohort Interview (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Laura Cohort Interview (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Amin Cohort Interview (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Rose Cohort Interview (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Kathy Cohort Interview (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Kathryn Kern Sr. Survey (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Romo, Jaime Jud (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Rosenzweig, Kathryn Anne (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Rosin, Alan Robert (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Rossen, Rebecca Anne (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Rudman, Lynn Ann (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Ryan, Jeffrey Kevin (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Saeta, David (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Safreno, Casey Douglas (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Samelson, Roger Morse (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Sanchez, Wayne Joseph (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Sarnoff, Linda Ann (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Sarnoff, Timothy Glenn (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Schmiesing, Clifford A. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Schmitz, Becky Lynn (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Shirley, William Alan (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Shoemaker, Jill Louise (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Sick, Robert Andrew (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Sillman, Jonathon Scott (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Sipe, David Michael (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Slater, Jonathan Stuart (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Smith, Charles Gerard (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Smith, Sandra Jean (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Vanessa Renee (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Sorenson, Glenn W., Jr. (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Spiro, Daniel Albert (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Squires, Latanya Renee (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Starr, Alexander P. (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Starr, Samuel Robert (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Stone, Allison C. (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Sugar, Karen J. (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Sutherland, Lori Dean (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Swanson, Mark Layne (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Taber, Evan Beth (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Taylor, Mark Robert (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Thamthitivat, Wanchai (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Tharp, Sidney Robert (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Timberlake, Todd Alex (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Titus, Patricia J. C. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Tomich, Laureen Anne (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Tompkins, Teresa Susan (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Townsley, David Boyd (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Tribe, Mark James (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Thukamoto, Kyle Satoshi (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Urdan, Jennifer Anne (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Vaguine, Andre (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Valadez, Jeanine Ann (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Van Oss, Mark Timothy (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Veitch, Jonathon Alan (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Voelcker, John R. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Volkmann, Kevin Eugene (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Walton, Nancy Elizabeth (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Watson, Brenda Sue (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Watson, Hanalee (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Watts, Emily Catherine (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Wells, Matthew Robert (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Wendland, Robert James (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - White, Kim Melanie (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Whitney, Kenneth Robert (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Wilkins, Michael Ian (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Wilkinson, Allen Lupton (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Williams, Kathryn (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Wong, Irwin Lane (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Wood, Christopher R. (Box 14, Folder 1)